foxhq.com 2004-04-02

# Entertainment & Arts :: Foxhq.com

**Privacy Policy**

**Foxhq.com PRIVACY POLICY**

We at Foxhq.com, our associates and affiliate website operators, pride ourselves on providing you, the customer, with a range of exciting online products and services. As part of this process, we may from time to time, ask you to provide us with certain personal information, for example, your name, date of birth, email address and credit card details.

**Protecting your privacy**

Foxhq.com takes all reasonable steps to protect the privacy of our customers and ensure that the personal information we collect is not ordinarily disclosed to third parties without the customer's consent.

However, there may be times when Foxhq.com may be required to disclose personal information of a customer without their express consent. This may occur where we have reason to believe that disclosing the information is

  * necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against the customer or another person who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) the rights or property of Foxhq.com or its associates, affiliates, other customers or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities, or  

  * required by law.

**WHY WE NEED TO OBTAIN PERSONAL INFORMATION ABOUT YOU**

Your personal information is used to enable us to deliver our online products and services to you. For example most of our products and services require some form of registration or subscription, while others require a payment to be made via a secure credit card facility. Your contact details may also be required from time to time to notify you of competition prizes you may have won.

Some of the information we collect, including that obtained from our customer feedback facilities, is used to help us develop and improve the quality of our products and services, which in turn, provides you with a more satisfying and enjoyable online experience.

**WHAT WE DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

Your email address and other personal information may be used to enable us to send you marketing or promotional material (such as promotional offers) on other products and services that we consider may be of interest to you. However, you may at any time, notify us that you do not wish to receive this material via an "opt-out" facility contained on our websites.

If you no longer wish us to keep a record of your personal information or you need to some of the particulars (for example, your address), you may contact us at the member information page on our websites or by emailing our Customer Support Group at [support@Foxhq.com](mailto:support@Foxhq.com), so we can correct, update or remove the information you have given us.

The information you provide to Foxhq.com is also shared among our subsidiaries and the operators of our affiliated websites.

Foxhq.com also shares collective information about our users (on an anonymous basis) with our advertisers, business partners, sponsors and other third parties. For example, we may disclose the fact that membership to one of our websites is "X" percent male and "Y" percent female.

This data is used to gain a better understanding of our customer base, thus enabling us to tailor our website content to our customers specific wants and needs.

**HOW WE COLLECT INFORMATION ABOUT YOU**

Foxhq.com may collect personal information about you and your surfing habits in a number of ways, including:

  * Directly from you, such as when you enter your personal details on our websites to register or subscribe to our services),  

  * Indirectly, by keeping a record of our users IP addresses and through the use of "cookies".

**Use of IP Addresses**

An IP address is a number that's automatically assigned to your computer whenever you're surfing the Web. Web servers, (the big computers that "serve up" Web pages) automatically identify your computer by its IP address.

We collect IP addresses for the purposes of system administration, to report aggregate information to our advertisers, and to audit the use of our site. When guests request pages from our sites, our servers may log the guests' IP addresses. We do not normally link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable, which means that a user's session will be logged, but the user remains anonymous to us. We can and will use IP addresses to identify a user when we feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with our house rules or terms of service or to protect our service, site, customers or others.

Some services provided by Foxhq.com, such as certain message boards, may display IP addresses along with the message poster's name and message. Please review each service prior to use and only uses those that disclose information you are comfortable with sharing.

**Use of Cookies**

What are cookies? Cookies are pieces of information that a Web site transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies make Web-surfing easier for you by saving your preferences while you're at our site. We never save passwords or credit card information in cookies. The use of cookies is an industry standard and you'll find them at most major Web sites.

By showing how and when guests use a site, cookies help us see which areas are popular and which are not. Many improvements and updates to the site are based on such data as total number of visitors and pages viewed. This information is most easily tracked with cookies. We use the information from cookies to provide services better tailored to our users needs.

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, note that some parts of the darkbluesea.com service will not function properly or may be considerably slower if you refuse cookies. For example, without cookies, you will not be able to set personalized news preferences or you may have difficulty completing shopping transactions, entering contests, or playing games.

You may also get cookies from our sponsors or advertisers websites. Neither Foxhq.com, nor our associates or affiliates have any control over this. 

**Use of Web Bugs**

What are web bugs ? A web bug is an electronic tag that is placed on a web page. It can be used to count the number of visitors to our sites and gather information and develop profiles about people who visit our site and/or click on links on our sites. Such devices are also known as 'invisible' or '1-by-1' GIFs due to their incredibly small size which usually cannot be detected. 

We use web bugs on our websites to track both the source and destination of visitors to our sites. This is required for proper accounting and reporting requirements of our affiliate program Dark Blue as well as to help us to provide our visitors with what they want to see and do online.

**PROTECTING KIDS PRIVACY**

Foxhq.com is committed to complying with the provisions of the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 and the Rules and Regulations made pursuant thereto. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children and to participate in the activities offered on our sites.

**Notice to Kids**

If you are under 13 years of age, we must get your parent or guardian's permission before we can collect any personal information about you, such as your name, date of birth, your hobbies, etc.

You are allowed to give us either your email address, or the email address of your parent or guardian, so that we can contact them and ask for their permission to collect your personal information. 

No other information about you should be given to us, or one of our websites, until your parent or guardian has given you permission.

**Notice to Parents**

Before your child can access most of the interactive products and services we provide, they are required to provide us with certain information about themselves, for example, their name, date of birth and contact details, so that we can register them as a member.

However, before we collect this personal information from your child, they are required to provide us with an e-mail address at which you, their parent or guardian can be contacted, so that we can obtain your consent.

Although users under 13 years of age may be allowed to participate in some contests and promotions, if they win, notification and prizes are sent to the parents or guardians at the address specified in the initial registration process. Publication of contest winners names, ages, or images for individuals under 13 require parental or guardian consent.

Subject to the below exemptions, the personal information that we collect from your children will be subject to and dealt with in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy.

No information collected from guests under 13 years of age is used for any marketing or promotional purposes whatsoever, either of Foxhq.com, our associates, affiliates or other third parties, unless expressly stated during the collection of this information or during registration for contests or promotions (and in that case, the information collected is used only for the specific contest or promotion).

We do not allow guests under 13 years of age to be listed in our member directory or to receive direct marketing communications from Foxhq.com, our associates, affiliates or other third parties.

**Links to Other Sites**

Users should be aware that on our affiliated websites, there are links to third party websites. If you "click" on a banner advertisement, a search result or another type of link contained on one of our sites, the "click" may result in you leaving our site and your browser being redirected to a website owned and controlled by a third party.

Neither Foxhq.com nor its subsidiaries have any control over and hence, accepts no responsibility for the content of these sites or the actions of the operators in relation to the collection of personal information of users of these sites.

While Foxhq.com, our associates and affiliates make every effort to protect your personal information and your privacy, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you disclose online and you do so at your own risk. Please keep in mind that whenever you give out personal information online, that information can be collected and used by people that neither we or you don't know.

**Your Acceptance of These Terms**

By using this website or our affiliated websites, you signify your assent to the terms and conditions contained herein (as amended from time to time). If you do not agree to be bound by its terms, we politely ask that you do not use this site.
